We gotta have discourse to get on course. So I've been seeing a lot of like really educated like
intelligent people say I'm not voting it's not happening. Respect. But I do think it would be
in our best interests right to just consider what the actual impact of that does. To actually like
get down to the bone bristle. Gristle? Of what is the true validity merit efficacy of voting. So I'm
gonna be doing that on November 19th in LA when I'm screening my political comedy documentary
In a Man That We Trust. I wanted to get some insight from some folks who are already on the inside
and uh we do trivia at the top. I pass out some free stuff. We watch the documentary then we do
a Q&A. And it's really gonna be a dope time because it's time for us to actually get in the
room together and off this internet and actually start having real discussions of finding a path
forward. So get your tickets at amandaseals.com November 19th at the Hollywood Improv 7 p.m.
And one more thing we're gonna be doing a drive with my home girl Miss Shirley Raines Beauty to
the Streets for folks down at Skid Row. They need men's shoes. So I would love if everybody who is
coming to the show can donate a pair of men's shoes. Shout out to Shirley Raines and the work
she's doing for the people.